bigsight.org 2013-03-14

# http://bigsight.org

Privacy Policy – June 26, 2008

Protecting your privacy is among out top concerns, and we believe that you should have control over what information is available about you online and how this information is used by third parties. This Privacy Policy covers our business, how our sites operate, and how we collect, store, use, and ultimately protect your privacy in connection with your use of Bigsight.org ( _[http://Bigsight.org](http://bigsight.org/)_ ) and a variety of applications we own and operate on Bigsight.

By visiting this site, you voluntarily consent to the terms outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our company sites.

## **Our Business: An editor-managed, public-facing people directory**

We own, operate, and manage a public-facing people directory at _[http://Bigsight.org](http://bigsight.org/)_. The goal of this site is to help users like you manage their online identity and share their work through a public-facing webpage hosted on our site. An individual’s personal information such as school, company, location, and affiliations are then linked to other pages on the site. Many of these pages appear high in search engine rankings. 

One key difference in our business relative to other people directories is that certain elements of our site are managed by an editor or team of editors. This difference is critical to how we approach and deal with privacy and personally identifiable information. There are four key differences:

_User-Managed Profile Network_

| 

_Editor-Managed, Public Directory of Profiles_  
  
---|---  
  
  * User has 100% editorial control of information 

  * User content must submit to few restrictions

  * User identity must be verified 

  * Site owners cannot build third party profiles

| 

  * User shares some editorial control with site editors

  * User content must adhere to form and design standards

  * Verification is at the discretion of site editors

  * Site editors may build third-party profiles

##  **The Information we Collect**

When you visit Bigsight you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Sites.

When you register with Bigsight, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, schools attended and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter Bigsight, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Bigsight visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Bigsight. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

When you use Bigsight, you may set up your personal profile, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, browse for jobs, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

You post User Content (as defined in the Bigsight Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. We do not restrict access to these data. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Bigsight is a violation of the Bigsight Terms of Service and should be reported to _[privacy@Bigsight.org](mailto:privacy@bigsight.org)_ .

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email or instant message inviting him or her to visit the site. Bigsight stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at _[info@Bigsight.org](mailto:info@bigsight.org)_ to request that we remove this information from our database.

Bigsight may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the Bigsight service through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. We may also use these data to further enrich your profile.

##  **Children Under Age 13**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Bigsight or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Bigsight. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [_info@Bigsight.org_](mailto:info@bigsight.org) .

##  **Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

##  **A Note about Importing Information from Facebook**

We provide multiple ways to create a profile on bigsight. One way to do this is by importing data from your Facebook account either through an application within Facebook or by using our importer based off of our homepage. By using these technologies you consent to having bigsight import your data and use it in accordance with our Privacy Policies and Terms of Use and to store the data indefinitely. These data are collected in accordance with your privacy settings inside Facebook. Your using the technologies serves as your active consent to these Terms.  

##  **Information Available to Public Search Engines**

Each profile is created to be open and publicly available on the Internet; as such, information submitted to us through the site quickly becomes part of a much larger public database of web pages. Because of this, profiles will likely appear in public search engines. These search engines often take "pictures" of each page and record past versions of them as "cached" copies of the site. This means that it is possible that search engines might present out-dated data for a profile; furthermore, should you elect to have your profile deleted at any time, we cannot guarantee that it will be deleted from third party databases. As such, we cannot be held liable for this cached information. 

##  **Limited Editorial and Content Control on Public Profiles**

We operate our site as a public directory; as such, we aim to ensure each profile adheres to standards of form and design that we set and can adjust at any time. These profiles are thus maintained by a team of Company-hired editors. While the editors aim to give as much content control as possible to the users, they retain the right to modify and adjust any profile at any time to adhere to our standards. Should you disagree with a specific edit, please contact [_editor@Bigsight.org_](mailto:editor@bigsight.org) to discuss this matter; if your request is not resolved and you remain displeased, you can have your profile deleted ([ _delete@Bigsight.org_](mailto:delete@bigsight.org) ).

##  **Use of Information Obtained by Bigsight**

When you register with Bigsight, you create your own profile and settings. Your profile information, as well as well as your name and photo, are displayed to all public web users. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by Bigsight that we think you may find valuable or updates on Bigsight members.

Profile information is used by Bigsight primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to other web users. In some cases where you interact with one of our features, you may permit other Bigsight users to augment your profile.

We may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message you may receive an email alerting you to that fact. Generally, you may opt out of such emails from the _[settings](http://www.facebook.com/editaccount.php?notifications)_ page, though Bigsight reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

Bigsight may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We may do this to customize advertising or target services. We believe this benefits you. You can know more about the world around you and, where there are advertisements, they're more likely to be interesting to you. For example, if you put a favorite movie in your profile, we might serve you an advertisement highlighting a screening of a similar one in your town. But we don't tell the movie company who you are.

We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, Bigsight Platform developers and other users of Bigsight, to supplement your profile. 

##  **Sharing your information with third parties**

Bigsight is interested in helping your share as much information as possible with the world. We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. For example:

  * We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Bigsight, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Bigsight-specified purposes.

  * We occasionally provide demonstration accounts that allow non-users a glimpse into the Bigsight world. Such accounts have only limited capabilities (e.g., messaging is disabled) and passwords are changed regularly to limit possible misuse.

  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Bigsight service or using the Bigsight name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

  * If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Bigsight’s business, or individual business units owned by Bigsight media group, Inc., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

When you use Bigsight , you are sharing information at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, or other items, this information may become publicly available.

## Links

Bigsight may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Bigsight.

## Third Party Advertising

At the moment, we do not serve advertisements on Bigsight; however, we plan to do so in the future. Advertisements that appear on Bigsight will be delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Bigsight does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Bigsight unless you choose to share it with them.

##  **Use of Information in Public Profiles**

As a user of the Company Sites you will have access to certain personal information. You agree to use this information for informational purposes only. If you are aware of someone mis-using the site or replicating profile content without permission of the Company, please report it to our editor ([ _editor@Bigsight.org_](mailto:editor@bigsight.org) ). 

## Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on Bigsight is readily available through the profile editing tools. Bigsight users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Bigsight account may do so on their user homepage. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to others.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals onBigsight, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another Bigsight user) you generally cannot remove such communications.

## Security

Bigsight takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of Bigsight, please contact us at _[privacy@Bigsight.org](mailto:privacy@bigsight.org)_

## Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of Bigsight, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Changes will take effect immediately. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

## Contacting Bigsight

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at _[privacy@Bigsight.org](mailto:privacy@bigsight.org)_ . You may also contact us by mail at 1201b 7th avenue north, Nashville, tn 37216 

**Updates:** The current statement was published on June 26, 2008. Any updates to this policy will be posted below.
